Dennis DeConcini Papers 1944-2008
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Congressional Activities. 1944-1998
  - Series 2: Legislative Committee Files. 1954-1994
    - Subseries 2: Appropriations. 1954-1994
      - Appropriations: Treasury, Postal Service, & General Government, 1977-1994
        - Postal Service: Clarksdale, Arizona. 1987 (Box 101, Folder 27)
        - Postal Service: Commerce Station, Arizona. 1988 (Box 101, Folder 28)
        - Postal Service: Deceptive Mailings. 1988-1989 (Box 101, Folder 29)
        - Postal Service: Desert Hills, Arizona. 1987 (Box 101, Folder 30)
        - Postal Service: Food Drive. 1991-1994 (Box 101, Folder 31)
        - Postal Service: General Correspondence. 1979-1984 (Box 101, Folder 32)
        - Postal Service: General Correspondence. 1982-1987 (Box 101, Folder 33)
        - Postal Service: General Correspondence. 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 34)
        - Postal Service: General Correspondence. 1988 (Box 101, Folder 35)
        - Postal Service: General Correspondence. 1991-1994 (Box 101, Folder 36)
        - Postal Service: General Correspondence, Retirement Communities. 1989-1990 (Box 102, Folder 1)
        - Postal Service: Hearing Materials. 1989 (Box 102, Folder 2)
        - Postal Service: Homeless Mail. 1991-1992 (Box 102, Folder 3)
        - Postal Service: Labor Relations. 1981 (Box 102, Folder 4)
        - Postal Service: Lessors. 1991 (Box 102, Folder 5)
        - Postal Service: Mail Fraud. 1990-1992 (Box 102, Folder 6)
        - Postal Service: Memos. 1981-1985 (Box 102, Folder 7)
        - Postal Service: National Association of Postmasters. 1987 (Box 102, Folder 8)
        - Postal Service: National Association of Postmasters. 1990 (Box 102, Folder 9)
        - Postal Service: National League of Postmasters. 1989 (Box 102, Folder 10)
        - Postal Service: Oro Valley, Arizona. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 11)
        - Postal Service: Perot Contract. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 12)
        - Postal Service: Police. 1993 (Box 102, Folder 13)
        - Postal Service: Postage-Free Election Material. 1984 (Box 102, Folder 14)
        - Postal Service: Prescott and Prescott Valley, Arizona. 1988-1991 (Box 102, Folder 15)
        - Postal Service: Privatization. 1987-1990 (Box 102, Folder 16)
        - Postal Service: Procurement. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 17)
        - Postal Service: Rate Increases. 1983-1991 (Box 102, Folder 18)
        - Postal Service: Revenue. 1987-1991 (Box 102, Folder 19)
        - Postal Service: Revenue. 1990-1992 (Box 102, Folder 20)
        - Postal Service: Revenue. 1991 (Box 102, Folder 21)
        - Postal Service: Revenue. 1992 (Box 102, Folder 22)
        - Postal Service: Safford, Arizona. 1986-1990 (Box 102, Folder 23)
        - Postal Service: Sam Hughes Neighborhood, Arizona. 1989 (Box 102, Folder 24)
        - Postal Service: Scottsdale, Arizona. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 25)
        - Postal Service: SCRAM Sonic Dog Repeller. 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 26)
        - Postal Service: Sierra Vista, Arizona. 1987 (Box 102, Folder 27)
        - Postal Service: Springville/Eager, Arizona. 1984 (Box 102, Folder 28)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Against Drunk Driving. 1989-1990 (Box 102, Folder 29)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Irving Berlin. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 30)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Senator Dennis Chavez. 1987 (Box 102, Folder 31)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Citizens' Advisory Committee. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 32)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Christopher Columbus. 1989 (Box 102, Folder 33)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Correspondence. 1983-1990 (Box 102, Folder 34)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Elvis. 1992 (Box 102, Folder 35)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Henry O. Flipper. 1986 (Box 102, Folder 36)
        - Postal Service Stamps: General Correspondence. 1988-1990 (Box 102, Folder 37)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Harry Hopkins. 1987 (Box 102, Folder 38)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Jewish Publication Society. 1987 (Box 102, Folder 39)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Kahil Gibran. 1987 (Box 102, Folder 40)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Life Underwriters. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 41)
        - Postal Service Stamps: Prescott Rodeo. 1985 (Box 102, Folder 42)
        - Postal Service Stamps: SCORE. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 43)
        - Postal Service: Stopping Unwanted Mail. 1986 (Box 102, Folder 44)
        - Postal Service: Sun City, Arizona. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 45)
        - Postal Service: Sun City West, Arizona. 1985-1993 (Box 102, Folder 46)
        - Postal Service: Toxins in Mail. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 47)
        - Postal Service: Unions. 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 48)
        - Postal Service: Velda Rose Contract Station. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 49)
        - Postal Service: Vernon (Closing). 1987 (Box 102, Folder 50)
        - Postal Service: Zip Codes. 1986-1989 (Box 102, Folder 51)
        - Railroad Retirement. 1983-1985 (Box 102, Folder 52)
        - Retirement Equity Act. 1984 (Box 102, Folder 53)
        - Senate Border Caucus. 1982-1983 (Box 103, Folder 1)
        - Senate Border Caucus. 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 2)
        - Treasury: General Correspondence. 1993 (Box 103, Folder 3)
        - Treasury: Meeting with Secretary Brady and John Robson. 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations: Veterans Administration-HUD, 1977-1994
        - HR 5313 Bill and Report Fiscal Year 1987. 1986 (Box 103, Folder 5)
        - Independent Agencies-Bill and Report Fiscal Year 1985. 1984 (Box 103, Folder 6)
        - Independent Agencies-Bill and Report Fiscal Year 1988. 1987 (Box 103, Folder 7-8)
        - Independent Agencies-Bill and Report Fiscal Year 1989. 1988 (Box 103, Folder 9)
        - Independent Agencies-Bill and Report Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 103, Folder 10)
        - Independent Agencies-Bill and Report Fiscal Year 1995. 1994 (Box 103, Folder 11)
        - Independent Agencies-Community Development Block Grants, Mesa, Arizona. 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 12)
        - Independent Agencies-Community Development Drachman School, Tucson, Arizona. 1993-1994 (Box 103, Folder 13)
        - Independent Agencies-Correspondence. 1980 (Box 103, Folder 14)
        - Independent Agencies-Correspondence. 1984 (Box 103, Folder 15)
        - Independent Agencies-Correspondence. 1985 (Box 103, Folder 16)
        - Independent Agencies-Correspondence. 1989-1993 (Box 103, Folder 17)
        - Independent Agencies-Empowerment Zones. 1993 (Box 103, Folder 18)
        - Independent Agencies-Empowerment Zones. 1994 (Box 103, Folder 19)
        - Independent Agencies-Enterprise Zones. 1981-1985 (Box 103, Folder 20)
        - Independent Agencies-Enterprise Zones. 1982 (Box 103, Folder 21)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency. 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 22)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency. 1979-1980 (Box 103, Folder 23)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Alaska Pulp Mills. 1984-1985 (Box 103, Folder 24)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Audit. 1989 (Box 103, Folder 25)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Avondale, Arizona. 1991-1993 (Box 103, Folder 26)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Border Environment. 1990-1991 (Box 103, Folder 27)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Border Environmental Issues. 1992 (Box 103, Folder 28)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Construction Grants. 1980 (Box 103, Folder 29)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Fiscal Year 1993. 1992 (Box 104, Folder 1)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Fiscal Year 1994. 1991-1993 (Box 104, Folder 2)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Fiscal Year 1991. 1990 (Box 104, Folder 3)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Pima County. 1992 (Box 104, Folder 4)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Safe Drinking Water Act. 1989-1993 (Box 104, Folder 5)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Superfund Reauthorization. 1984-1986 (Box 104, Folder 6)
        - Independent Agencies-Environmental Protection Agency, Water Quality Research Project. 1993 (Box 104, Folder 7)
        - Independent Agencies-Ethanol Amendment. 1994 (Box 104, Folder 8)
        - Independent Agencies-Fair Housing (Hearing Materials). 1985 (Box 104, Folder 9)
        - Independent Agencies-Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA). 1984-1986 (Box 104, Folder 10)
        - Independent Agencies-FEMA, Phoenix Search and Rescue. 1993 (Box 104, Folder 11)
        - Independent Agencies-FEMA, Pima County Problems. 1988-1991 (Box 104, Folder 12)
        - Independent Agencies-FEMA Supplemental Funding. 1988-1991 (Box 104, Folder 13)
        - Independent Agencies-FEMA, Gila Valley Irrigation District Flooding. 1982 (Box 104, Folder 14)
        - Independent Agencies-Homeless. 1987-1990 (Box 104, Folder 15)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing, Arizona's Legislative Priorities. 1994 (Box 104, Folder 16)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing, Avondale, Arizona. 1988 (Box 104, Folder 17)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing Background. 1988-1990 (Box 104, Folder 18)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing Correspondence. 1978-1980 (Box 104, Folder 19)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing Correspondence. 1979-1982 (Box 104, Folder 20)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing Correspondence. 1988-1990 (Box 104, Folder 21)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing Correspondence. 1993 (Box 104, Folder 22)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing Correspondence. 1993-1994 (Box 104, Folder 23)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing Occupancy Standards. 1988-1994 (Box 104, Folder 24)
        - Independent Agencies-HUD and Supplemental Funding. 1983-1984 (Box 104, Folder 25)
        - Independent Agencies-Housing, Hurst Plan. 1993 (Box 104, Folder 26)
        - Independent Agencies-Murkowski/DeConcini Amendment. 1985 (Box 105, Folder 1)
        - Independent Agencies-NASA, Shuttle Infrared Telescope Facility. 1984 (Box 105, Folder 2)
        - Independent Agencies-Occupational Safety and Health Administration. 1989 (Box 105, Folder 3)
        - Independent Agencies-Public Housing Trends. 1988 (Box 105, Folder 4)
        - Independent Agencies-Real Estate Settlement Procedures Act. 1988-1989 (Box 105, Folder 5)
        - Independent Agencies-Requests Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 105, Folder 6)
        - Independent Agencies-Requests Fiscal Year 1995. 1994 (Box 105, Folder 7)
        - Independent Agencies-Revenue Sharing Phase Out. 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 8)
        - Independent Agencies-Space Science Fiscal Year 1990. 1989 (Box 105, Folder 9)
        - Independent Agencies-Space and Technology. 1989-1991 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Subseries 3: Banking, Housing & Urban Affairs, 1970-1994
      - Affordable Housing Act. 1989 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - American Technology and Trade Banking System. 1990 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Arizona Stock Exchange. 1993 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Bank of America Corporation. 1991-1993 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Bank Bribery. 1986 (Box 105, Folder 15)
      - Bank Bribery Legislation. 1985 (Box 105, Folder 16)
      - Bank Deregulation Bill. 1984 (Box 105, Folder 17)
      - Bank Reform. 1991 (Box 105, Folder 18)
      - Banking Deregulation Bill. 1984 (Box 105, Folder 19)
      - Banking Reform Binder. 1991 (Box 105, Folder 20)
      - Banking Reform, Financial Institutions Reform Recovery and Enforcement Act. 1989 (Box 105, Folder 21)
      - Banks and Credit Unions. 1990-1992 (Box 105, Folder 22)
      - Brokered Deposits. 1984 (Box 105, Folder 23)
      - Budget Resolution. 1993 (Box 105, Folder 24)
      - Check Cashing-Lifeline Service. 1990 (Box 105, Folder 25)
      - Check Clearance. 1983-1986 (Box 105, Folder 26)
      - Colonias. 1988 (Box 105, Folder 27)
      - Columbus Coin Bill. 1987 (Box 105, Folder 28)
      - Community Development Block Awards. 1986 (Box 105, Folder 29)
      - Congressional Accountability Act. 1994 (Box 105, Folder 30)
      - Consumer Reporting Reform. 1994 (Box 105, Folder 31)
      - Constituent Correspondence. 1980-1981 (Box 105, Folder 32)
      - Continental Bank Bailouts. 1984 (Box 105, Folder 33)
      - Credit Card Charges. 1992 (Box 105, Folder 34)
      - Credit Card Interest. 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 35)
      - Credit Card Surcharges. 1984 (Box 105, Folder 36)
      - Currency. 1983 (Box 105, Folder 37)
      - Domenici Junk Bond Bill. 1985 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Defense Production Act. 1982-1983 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Defense Revitalization. 1981 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Derivatives. 1994 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Emergency Home Purchase Assistance. 1979-1989 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Emergency Homeowners Relief Act. 1982-1983 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Equitable Escheatment Act. 1994 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - EX-IM Bank Bill. 1986 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Export Administration Act. 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Export-Import Bank. 1988 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Fair Housing. 1986 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Federal Home Loan Bank Board. 1985 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Federal Housing Administration. 1989-1991 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Federal Housing Administration Loan Limits. 1988-1990 (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - Federal Housing Administration, Pinal County. 1989-1990 (Box 106, Folder 15)
      - Federal Housing Administration, Reverse Mortgages. 1983-1993 (Box 106, Folder 16)
      - Federal Reserve. 1982-1983 (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - Federal Reserve Statistical Release. 1983-1985 (Box 106, Folder 18)
      - FIEQ-ATVF. 1993-1994 (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - Financial Institutions. 1970-1980 (Box 106, Folder 20)
      - Financial Institutions Equity Act. 1980-1985 (Box 106, Folder 21)
      - Financial Institution Restructure. 1985-1988 (Box 106, Folder 22)
      - Flood Insurance. 1992-1994 (Box 106, Folder 23)
      - Foreign Corrupt Practices Act. 1983 (Box 106, Folder 24)
      - Garn Banking Bill. 1986 (Box 106, Folder 25)
      - Gray, Ed. 1986 (Box 106, Folder 26)
      - Hostile Takeovers. 1987-1988 (Box 106, Folder 27)
      - Housing (Background). 1988-1989 (Box 106, Folder 28)
      - Housing Bill. 1987-1988 (Box 106, Folder 29)
      - Housing, Mesa. 1994 (Box 106, Folder 30)
      - Housing Opportunity Grant. 1987-1988 (Box 106, Folder 31)
      - Housing Policy. 1988-1989 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Housing and Urban-Rural Recovery Act. 1982-1983 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Hutton, E.F. 1985 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Insurance. 1993-1994 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Interstate Banking. 1991-1994 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Junk Bonds. 1985-1986 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Law Enforcement Coin Act. 1992 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Lincoln Thrift. 1977 (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Lindsey, Lawrence (Federal Reserve Board Nom.). 1991 (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Low Income Housing. 1983 (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - Manufactured Housing. 1983-1985 (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Manufactured Housing. 1987 (Box 107, Folder 12)
      - McCain Pork Bill. 1991 (Box 107, Folder 13)
      - Mexican Accounts in American Banks. 1982-1983 (Box 107, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous. 1985-1992 (Box 107, Folder 15)
      - Monetary Control Act of 1980. 1979-1983 (Box 107, Folder 16)
      - Money Laundering. 1984 (Box 107, Folder 17)
      - Money Magazine. 1990 (Box 107, Folder 18)
      - Mortgage Interest Deduction. 1989 (Box 107, Folder 19)
      - Multilateral Investment Fund, Georgetown Proposal. 1992-1994 (Box 107, Folder 20)
      - Mutual to Stock Conversions. 1984 (Box 107, Folder 21)
      - NAD Bank. 1993 (Box 107, Folder 22)
      - National Housing Act, Section 232. 1983 (Box 107, Folder 23)
      - Non-Bank Banks. 1980-1985 (Box 107, Folder 24)
      - Non-Banks, Dreyfus. 1983 (Box 107, Folder 25)
      - Norwest/Citibank. 1993 (Box 107, Folder 26)
      - RTC Affordable Housing. 1989-1992 (Box 107, Folder 27)
      - Savings Bonds. 1984 (Box 107, Folder 28)
      - Secondary Mortgage. 1983 (Box 107, Folder 29)
      - Securities and Exchange. 1983 (Box 107, Folder 30)
      - Seidman, L. William FDIC Nomination. 1985 (Box 107, Folder 31)
      - Silver Stockpile. 1983 (Box 107, Folder 32)
      - South African Kruggerands. 1985 (Box 107, Folder 33)
      - S. 69. 1977 (Box 107, Folder 34)
      - S. 664. 1977 (Box 107, Folder 35)
      - S. 1720. 1980 (Box 107, Folder 36)
      - S. 1737. 1977 (Box 107, Folder 37)
      - TAMCO Financial Corp. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 38)
      - Trust for Investment in Mortgages. 1983-1984 (Box 107, Folder 39)
      - Union Savings. 1984 (Box 107, Folder 40)
      - Unitary Thrift Holding Companies. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 41)
      - Urban Development Action Grants (UDAG). 1984-1985 (Box 107, Folder 42)
      - Urban Policy and the New Federalism. 1981-1983 (Box 107, Folder 43)
      - Valley National/Bank One. 1992 (Box 107, Folder 44)
      - Volcker and Fed-Critical Report. 1980 (Box 107, Folder 45)
      - Weekly Economic Review Date. 1983 (Box 107, Folder 46)
      - Western Savings. 1988 (Box 107, Folder 47)
      - Whitewater. 1994 (Box 107, Folder 48)
      - Whitewater Independent Counsel. 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Subseries 4: Budget, 1980-1994
      - Additional Cut Information. 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Bills Fiscal Year 1986. 1985 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Articles on Fiscal Year 1986. 1986 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Boschwitz-Boren Budget Plan. 1985 (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Budget Agreement Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 6-7)
      - Budget Amendments Fiscal Year 1986. 1985 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Budget Articles. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Budget Background, Congressional Research Service. 1989-1993 (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Budget Background, Correspondence, and Memos. 1990-1993 (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Budget Correspondence, Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - Budget Cuts, Bumpers Cut Language. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 13)
      - Budget Cuts, Fiscal Years 1993-1994, Kerry's Cut Lists. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 14)
      - Budget Cuts, Penny-Kasich Press Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 15)
      - Budget Cuts, Repeal of Senate Cost of Living Adjustment. 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 16)
      - Budget Cutting Rescission and Rescission Procedures Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 17)
      - Budget Facts and Figures. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 18)
      - Budget Facts and Figures, Whitehouse. 1993 (Box 108, Folder 19)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1983 (Background). 1981-1982 (Box 108, Folder 20)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1984. 1983 (Box 108, Folder 21)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1984 (Background). 1983 (Box 108, Folder 22)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1985. 1984 (Box 108, Folder 23)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1986. 1985 (Box 108, Folder 24)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1986 (Background). 1985 (Box 108, Folder 25)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1987 (Background). 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 26)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1990 (Background). 1988-1989 (Box 108, Folder 27)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1990 Briefing Book. 1989 (Box 108, Folder 28)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1991. 1989-1990 (Box 108, Folder 29)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1991 (Background). 1990 (Box 108, Folder 30)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1992. 1991 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1992 Briefing Book. 1991 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1992 Correspondence. 1991 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1993. 1992 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Budget Fiscal Year 1995. 1994 (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Budget Freeze Proposal Fiscal Year 1986. 1985 (Box 109, Folder 6-7)
      - Budget Impact, Phoenix. 1985 (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - Budget Process and Reconciliation. 1984-1990 (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Budget Proposals (Alternatives). 1993 (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - Budget Reconciliation. 1990 (Box 109, Folder 11)
      - Budget Reconciliation. 1993 (Box 109, Folder 12-14)
      - Budget Reconciliation, Final Passage of Clinton Plan. 1993 (Box 109, Folder 15)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1986. 1985 (Box 109, Folder 16)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1987. 1986 (Box 109, Folder 17)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1988 Briefing Book. 1987 (Box 109, Folder 18-19)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1990 Briefing Book. 1989 (Box 109, Folder 20)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1991. 1990 (Box 109, Folder 21-23)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1991 Briefing Book. 1990 (Box 110, Folder 1-2)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1991 Congressional Research Service Reports. 1985-1987 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 4-5)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 Articles. 1993-1994 (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 Background. 1982-1993 (Box 110, Folder 7-8)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 Committee Print. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 Comparison of Renewal Provisions. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 Interest Group Letters. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 11-12)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 Memos and Correspondence. 1993-1994 (Box 110, Folder 13)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 Small Business. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 14)
      - Budget Reconciliation Fiscal Year 1994 White House Democratic Policy Committee. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Budget Resolution Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 110, Folder 16-17)
      - Budget Resolution Fiscal Year 1995. 1994 (Box 110, Folder 18)
      - Budget Resolutions and Rescissions. 1992 (Box 110, Folder 19)
      - Budget Summit Agreement: Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act Fiscal Year 1991. 1990 (Box 110, Folder 20)
      - Budget of the United States of America. 1978 (Box 110, Folder 21)
      - Budget of the United States Government. 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Budget of the United States Government: Analytical Perspectives. 1995 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Budget of the United States Government: Appendix. 1995 (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Budget of the United States Government: Historical Tables. 1995 (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Budget Vote, Reconciliation Bill. 1993 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Bush Budget Proposals. 1991 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Bush Budget Proposals Fiscal Year 1991. 1990 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Byrd Compromise: Budget Plan. 1985 (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - Chiles and Chiles/Hollings Budget Plan. 1985 (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - Clinton Budget Proposals. 1993 (Box 111, Folder 10)
      - Congressional Budget Office Estimates. 1993 (Box 111, Folder 11-12)
      - Correspondence and Memos. 1984-1994 (Box 111, Folder 13)
      - Deadlines, Process Interest Fiscal Year 1992. 1991 (Box 111, Folder 14)
      - Debt Busters. 1993 (Box 111, Folder 15)
      - Deficit Reduction Fiscal Year 1986. 1985 (Box 111, Folder 16-17)
      - Deficit Reduction Proposal. 1993 (Box 111, Folder 18)
      - Deficit Trust Fund Debate. 1993 (Box 111, Folder 19)
      - Economic Stimulus Plan. 1992-1993 (Box 111, Folder 20)
      - Economic Stimulus Plan. 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
      - General, Jobs Bill. 1977-1980 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - GOP/Hutchinson. 1993 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Graham Deficit Reduction Group. 1992-1993 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Gramm/Rudman/Hollings. 1986 (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Greenstein Criticism. 1993 (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - Impact of Proposed Budget on Cities. 1985 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - Kasich Material. 1993 (Box 112, Folder 10)